<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>startup on NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System User Guide</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/tags/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in startup on NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System User Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:15:33 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/tags/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Startup Procedure</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/startup_procedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/startup_procedure/</guid>
      <description>WARNING System isolation from mains is achieved through detachment of power cord. Turn OFF the power switch and unplug the power cord from wall outlet to achieve isolation from mains. Do not bypass the isolation transformer and connect any of the NGENUITY™ components directly to a wall outlet. To avoid risk of electric shock, this equipment must only be connected to a supply mains with protective earth (ground). The system should be connected to an uninterruptible power source when loss of power would result in an unacceptable risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Movement</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/system_movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/system_movement/</guid>
      <description>CAUTIONDo not push or pull unit by the display or any cable. The unit should be pulled and not pushed, especially over elevator and door thresholds.To move the system around the room, unlock the casters. Each castor on the cart has three modes, controlled by the brake pedal. Set each castor in total lock mode while the system is being used.
 The casters do not rotate    Unlocked    Total Lock   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Articulation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/display_articulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/display_articulation/</guid>
      <description>The display moves up or down the mast, rotates side to side, and tilts back or forth. Only grasp the bottom or sides of the display while adjusting it. Avoid putting stress on the top of the display.
NOTICEIf necessary, loosen the adjustment knobs on the display mounting bracket to adjust the tilt and tighten them to secure it. Do not remove the adjustment knobs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
