<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NGENUITY 3D Visualization System on NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System User Guide</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NGENUITY 3D Visualization System on NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System User Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:16:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>General Information</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/front_matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 04:28:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/front_matter/</guid>
      <description>Manufacturer   Manufacturer:
Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
6201 South Freeway
Fort Worth, TX 76134-2099, USA
Made in the USA with global materials
Produced By:
Alcon Research, LLC.
15800 Alcon Parkway
Irvine, CA 92618-3818, USA
 European Representative   Alcon Laboratories Belgium
Lichterveld 3
2870 Puurs-Sint-Amands
Belgium
US Pat: www.alconpatents.com
 CE Mark    Medical Device Symbol    Prescription Only   Catalog number: 8065000112 Rev.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:34:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/terms/</guid>
      <description>The following terms are used in this guide or in the application:
 System - The NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System, including the cart, display, and camera. Constellation™ - The Constellation™ Vision System Centurion™ - The Centurion™ Vision System K600 keyboard - The Logitech1 K600 wireless keyboard (select countries only) K830 keyboard - The Logitech1 K830 wireless keyboard ORA SYSTEM™ - The ORA SYSTEM™ with VerifEye™ + Technology    Trademarks are property of their respective owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abbreviations and Acronyms</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/abbreviations_and_acronyms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:34:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/abbreviations_and_acronyms/</guid>
      <description>The following abbreviations and acronyms appear in this guide or in the application:
 2D - 2-dimensional 3D - 3-dimensional AC - Alternating current EPU - Embedded processing unit PiP - Picture-in-picture layout USB - Universal serial bus  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/guide_overview/symbols/</guid>
      <description>The following symbols and icons are used on the system and in labels:
 Main power switch - on position    Main power switch - off position    AC current input    Safety Warning    Risk of Electric Shock    Manufacturer    Intertek NRTL mark    European Conformity mark    Authorized representative in the European community    Equipment should not be disposed of in domestic household waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Description</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/system_description/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:35:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/system_description/</guid>
      <description>The Alcon NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is a 3D stereoscopic, high-definition digital video camera and workstation that operates as an adjunct to a surgical microscope during surgery. The system displays real-time images or images from recordings on a flat-panel, high-definition digital 3D display device, positioned for viewing video. There is no additional light (or energy) delivered by the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intended Use</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/intended_use/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/intended_use/</guid>
      <description>The NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is intended to aid trained surgeons in visualization during ophthalmic surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indications for Use</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/indications_for_use/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:37:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/indications_for_use/</guid>
      <description>The NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is indicated for providing magnified stereoscopic images of objects in real time or from recordings. It may also display non-diagnostic information from validated Alcon systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contraindications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/contraindications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/contraindications/</guid>
      <description>There are no contraindications at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Benefits</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/clinical_benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:37:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/clinical_benefits/</guid>
      <description>The intended clinical benefit of the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is to allow users to visualize ophthalmic surgery by looking at a display screen rather than in standard microscope oculars for improved ergonomic benefit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Considerations</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/environmental_considerations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:37:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_overview/environmental_considerations/</guid>
      <description>Keep the system dry and protect it from harmful ingress of water. The camera includes a rating of IPX1: protection against vertically falling drops of water. See Specifications for temperature and humidity considerations.
WARNINGTo prevent fire or shock hazard, do not expose system to rain or moisture. This system is not suitable for use in the presence of flammable anesthetics mixture with air or with oxygen. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Safety Information</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/safety_information/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:37:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/safety_information/</guid>
      <description>In addition to reading this user guide, all users must be trained by an Alcon employee or a trainer that has been designated by Alcon. The trainee must be comfortable working as an interface between the doctor and the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System, and the trainee must be familiar with pre-operative room and operating room protocols.
For customers in the U.S.A.
Federal Law restricts this device to sale by or on the order of a licensed medical practitioner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Warnings and Precautions</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/general_warnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/general_warnings/</guid>
      <description>Pay close attention to warnings and cautions. A warning statement is written to protect individuals from bodily harm. A caution statement is written to protect the instrument from damage. This section is for general system warnings and precautions only.
WARNING In case of a deficiency, do not use the system; call Alcon Technical Services. Use of accessories other than those provided may affect system performance and create potential hazards. If it is determined that an accessory not provided by Alcon has contributed to the malfunction of the equipment during the warranty period, service will be provided at prevailing hourly rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Warranty</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/warranty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/warranty/</guid>
      <description>Alcon Laboratories, Inc., will repair or replace at its option, any system or accompanying accessories found to be defective in material and/or workmanship for a period of one (1) year from the date of initial installation. This warranty applies to the original purchaser of the system, when said system is properly installed, maintained, and operated in accordance with published instructions.
Alcon Laboratories shall not be obligated to provide services under this warranty for damage to or destruction of systems covered where such damage or destruction is (i) a result of or caused by fire or explosion of any origin, riot, civil commotion, aircraft, war, or any Act of God including, but not limited to lightning, windstorm, hail, flood, earthquake, or (ii) caused by customer’s misuse or improper servicing of said systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/camera/</guid>
      <description>The camera is a stereoscopic 3D camera with high dynamic range. Mount the camera on a surgical microscope.
1 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures video from the connected microscope.  2 Strain relief screw &amp;ndash; Holds the camera cable in place to reduce stress on the cable connection.  3 USB camera connector &amp;ndash; Connects the camera to the cart.  4 Iris slider &amp;ndash; Adjusts light exposure captured by the camera. Alcon recommends setting the iris slider to 30%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cart</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/cart/</guid>
      <description>The cart receives video input from the camera and additional data from other connected devices, and then outputs the results on the monitor.
1 Primary Display &amp;ndash; Produces 3840 x 2160p 3D resolution video. 3D images require passive, circularly-polarized 3D glasses.  2 Touchpad &amp;ndash; Controls the cursor on the display. Another touchpad is also available on the wireless keyboard.  3 Front panel connectors &amp;ndash; Includes 2 USB, an HDMI output, and a composite connector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Displays</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/displays/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/displays/</guid>
      <description>Depending on the display model, the system connects to the display either through DisplayPort input 1 or both the HDMI input 3 and COMM cable connector. The system also supports a secondary display to either duplicate the primary display view or show a subset of features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glasses</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/glasses/</guid>
      <description>3D images require passive, circularly-polarized 3D glasses. If necessary, wear the 3D glasses over prescription glasses.
CAUTION To ensure optimal image quality, the system should only be used with Alcon-supplied 3D glasses. Contact Alcon if additional pairs are required. Polarized prescription glasses will distort the 3D effect and should not be used. The 3D glasses must be worn in front of the laser protective eyewear to avoid distorting the 3D effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard and Mouse</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/keyboard_and_mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/keyboard_and_mouse/</guid>
      <description>The system includes both a wired and a wireless keyboard with an integrated touchpad. The wireless keyboard is rechargeable and the battery indicator displays the charge level while the keyboard is on.
1 Power indicator &amp;ndash; Lights according to the battery status   Blinking green - The battery is charging. Solid green – The battery has adequate charge. Blinking red – The battery power is low. Recharge the battery.  2 USB connector (rear) &amp;ndash; Connects the keyboard to a power source to recharge the batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datafusion</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/datafusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/datafusion/</guid>
      <description>The Constellation™, Centurion™, and ORA SYSTEM™ provide additional patient and surgical operation information to display on the system. The Constellation™ and Centurion™ systems displays the information on the surgical screen while the ORA SYSTEM™ displays the information in PiP or split screen layouts. The Constellation™ also controls basic system functions. The ORA SYSTEM™ dynamic reticle displays on the live image (activate on the ORA SYSTEM™).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Footswitch (Optional)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</guid>
      <description>The footswitch performs basic functions during operation through controls operated by a foot.
1 Left push button &amp;ndash; Changes the camera orientation between standard and inverted.  2 Right push button &amp;ndash; Starts or stops movie recordings.  3 Left pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the previous imaging mode.  4 Right pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the next imaging mode.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessories</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/accessories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/system_components/accessories/</guid>
      <description>The system may include the following accessories:
 Lens cap - Protects the camera lens. Cable straps - Secure the camera cable to the microscope. Cable hooks - Route loose cables or coil cable for storage or transportation. Display remote and batteries - Sets the display settings. Use only if directed by Technical Services. The remote may require AA or AAA batteries depending on the display modal. Screen protector - Protects the display when the system is in storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Specifications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/specifications/general_specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/specifications/general_specifications/</guid>
      <description>   Topic Value     Weight (unpacked) 133 kg (294 lb)   Weight (packed) 333 kg (734 lb)   Dimensions (unpacked) 82.6 cm L x 122.7 cm W x 193.8 cm H (32.5” L x 48.3” W x 76.3” H)   Dimensions (packed) 106.7 cm L x 153.2 cm W x 177.3 cm H (42” L x 60.3” W x 69.8” H)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Specifications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/specifications/environmental_specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/specifications/environmental_specifications/</guid>
      <description>   Topic Value     Temperature (operating) 5 °C to 30 °C (41 °F to 86 °F)   Temperature (storage and transport) 0 °C to 50 °C (32 °F to 122 °F)   Relative humidity (operating) 15% to 85% non-condensing   Relative humidty (storage and transport) 10% to 90% non-condensing   Atmospheric pressure 100 to 75 kPa   Atmospheric pressure 100 to 30 kPa    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Installation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/camera_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/camera_installation/</guid>
      <description>WARNINGIn case of emergency, keep the microscope oculars and mounting accessories in the cart top drawer. If there are any concerns regarding the continued safe use of the system, consider returning to the oculars.Mount the camera to a surgical microscope. Depending on the microscope model, install either a Z-ring or L-ring bracket to the camera lens (see the letters in the image below). The Z-ring bracket is for Alcon or Zeiss™ microscopes and the L-ring bracket is for Leica™ microscopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constellation™ Connection</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/constellation_connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/constellation_connection/</guid>
      <description>WARNINGOnly the Constellation&amp;trade; Vision System should be connected to an Ethernet port on the embedded processing unit (EPU) during normal system operation. The other Ethernet ports are for maintenance purposes only.Connect the Ethernet cable from the system to the Constellation™ Ethernet connector and setup DataFusion settings on the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centurion™ Connection</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/centurion_connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:06:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/centurion_connection/</guid>
      <description>Enable wireless communication on the Centurion™ and setup DataFusion settings on the system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORA SYSTEM™ Connection</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/ora_system_connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:06:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/datafusion_connections/ora_system_connection/</guid>
      <description>Connect the provided HDMI cable to the HDMI output connector on the ORA SYSTEM™.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Display (Optional)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/secondary_display/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:09:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_assembly/secondary_display/</guid>
      <description>To connect a secondary display, connect the it to the HDMI output connector on the system front panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Procedure</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/startup_procedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/startup_procedure/</guid>
      <description>WARNING System isolation from mains is achieved through detachment of power cord. Turn OFF the power switch and unplug the power cord from wall outlet to achieve isolation from mains. Do not bypass the isolation transformer and connect any of the NGENUITY™ components directly to a wall outlet. To avoid risk of electric shock, this equipment must only be connected to a supply mains with protective earth (ground). The system should be connected to an uninterruptible power source when loss of power would result in an unacceptable risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Movement</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/system_movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/system_movement/</guid>
      <description>CAUTIONDo not push or pull unit by the display or any cable. The unit should be pulled and not pushed, especially over elevator and door thresholds.To move the system around the room, unlock the casters. Each castor on the cart has three modes, controlled by the brake pedal. Set each castor in total lock mode while the system is being used.
 The casters do not rotate    Unlocked    Total Lock   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Articulation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/display_articulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/display_articulation/</guid>
      <description>The display moves up or down the mast, rotates side to side, and tilts back or forth. Only grasp the bottom or sides of the display while adjusting it. Avoid putting stress on the top of the display.
NOTICEIf necessary, loosen the adjustment knobs on the display mounting bracket to adjust the tilt and tighten them to secure it. Do not remove the adjustment knobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Optimization</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/view_optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/system_position/view_optimization/</guid>
      <description>For the best 3D effect, place the display next to the patient bed, between 4′ to 6′ (1.2 m to 1.8 m) away from the user. Depending on the display, align either the bottom third or middle of the display perpendicular with the line of sight of the seated user. If necessary, also ensure other viewers have a satisfactory view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Sensor Initialization</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/camera_confoguration/sensor_initialization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/camera_confoguration/sensor_initialization/</guid>
      <description>Sensor initialization helps prevent image degradation and noise. Perform the following steps during startup or after camera connection. A message to expose the camera to more light appears.
NOTICEImage quality is also influenced by other factors.  Turn on all room lights.
  Open the camera iris to 100%.
  Position the white balance card at 90 degrees under the microscope objective lens. The message disappears within 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Pan</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/camera_confoguration/camera_pan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/camera_confoguration/camera_pan/</guid>
      <description>The camera pan function adjusts the alignment of the image without moving the camera or microscope mount. The range of image movement is limited.
The pan function is useful in the following cases:
 In retina cases, where the wide angle lens is not centered in the optical path. In minimally invasive glaucoma surgery (MIGS) procedures when gonioscopy lens image is not centered in optical path.  Use Ctrl+Up, Ctrl+Right, Ctrl+Down, or Ctrl+Left to electronically move the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Balance</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/white_balance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/white_balance/</guid>
      <description>To calibrate light settings, verify the light temperature and perform the white balance procedure (see Light Profile Settings). Before setting white balance, perform the following checks:
 Set the camera iris slider to normal working conditions for the user. Alcon recommends 30%. Set the microscope to maximum zoom. Disable any red reflex settings. Remove all extraneous devices (for example, beam splitters or invertors). Disable any unique microscope filtration or lens settings (for example, laser filters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/setup_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_setup/setup_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>To extend the depth of field and improve performance at high magnification, follow these tips:
 Parfocalize visualization (microscope, non-contact, contact) to focus the surgical space. Zoom in to fill the display to maximize the quality of surgical view.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/software_overview/navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:21:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/software_overview/navigation/</guid>
      <description>The following icons appear throughout the interface.
 Indicates the touchpad cursor location.    Saves the pending changes and closes the dialog box. Switching to a different setting panel saves any pending changes.    Closes the dialog box and does not save pending changes.    Opens another dialog box to change additional settings.    Saves settings to a connected USB drive.    Opens the next screen or dialog box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Screen Layout</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/software_overview/home_screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:22:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/software_overview/home_screen/</guid>
      <description>1 Home panel &amp;ndash; Contains menus to manage doctor profiles, add or delete patient profiles, and start a case.  2 Shutdown button &amp;ndash; Turns off the system.  3 System Settings button &amp;ndash; Opens the system settings options (see System Settings).  4 Media Management App button &amp;ndash; Opens an application to view and edit recorded video and snapshots.  5 Eject Drive button &amp;ndash; Safely ejects a connected hard drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Doctor Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/add_doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/add_doctor/</guid>
      <description>To create a new doctor profile, perform the following:
 In the Home panel, select the doctor Add button. The New Doctor dialog box opens. In the Name field, enter a profile name. To copy settings from another profile, perform the following:  Click the Copy Settings From toggle switch. Click Local to copy a profile stored on the system or click USB to copy a profile from a connected USB drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete Doctor Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/delete_doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/delete_doctor/</guid>
      <description> In the Home panel, select a doctor profile. Click the doctor Delete button. Click Confirm.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Doctor Profile Settings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/set_doctor_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/set_doctor_settings/</guid>
      <description> In the Home panel, select a doctor profile. Click Doctor Defaults. Perform one of the following:  Click Save all to save the current settings as the profile default settings. Click Restore all to set the current settings to the saved profile default settings.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export Doctor Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/export_doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/doctor_management/export_doctor/</guid>
      <description> Connect a USB drive to a USB connector. In the Home panel, select a doctor profile. Click Export Doctor.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Patient Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/patient_management/add_patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/patient_management/add_patient/</guid>
      <description>In the Home panel, select the patient Add button. The Patient Information dialog box opens. Enter a first and last name. Select one of the following:  OD – right eye OS – left eye   To add a date of birth, patient ID name, or procedure, click Optional Data. a. In the Date of Birth field, enter a year, month, and day. b. In the ID field, enter a unique identification code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete Patient Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/patient_management/delete_patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:24:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/patient_management/delete_patient/</guid>
      <description> In the Home panel, select a patient profile. Click the patient Delete button. Click Confirm.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procedure Screen Layout</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/procedure_layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/procedure_layout/</guid>
      <description>1 Case timer &amp;ndash; Displays the duration of the surgical case.  2 Record video button &amp;ndash; Starts and stops recording video of the screen. A red dot appears next to the case when a case is being recorded.  3 Snapshot button &amp;ndash; Takes a picture of the screen.  4 Information panel &amp;ndash; Displays basic information to identify the current patient and case.  5 Quick Access Bar &amp;ndash; Includes buttons to quickly change various display settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recordings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/recordings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/recordings/</guid>
      <description>Recordings save video from the camera. To save overlay information, enable the applicable DataFusion feature. Overlay information includes patient and case information from the system, or other data from connected systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Access Bar</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/quick_access_bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/live_case/quick_access_bar/</guid>
      <description>The Quick Access Bar contains specified buttons for display options. Click the buttons to quickly change settings or, if available, click the drop-down menu below buttons to select a specific option.
To change the available buttons or the options available for a button, see Settings.
Use the Quick Access Bar to change the following display modes and settings:
1 Swap layout &amp;ndash; Changes the number of video inputs displayed on the Case screen (1 or 2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End Case</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/end_case/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/end_case/</guid>
      <description>When the case is complete, click End Case. Recordings stop and the following prompts appear:
 If any imaging mode changes were made during the case, select Yes to save the changes or No to delete the changes. If desired, save recorded video. To save a copy of the video to an external hard drive, connect one to a side panel USB connector. If a patient profile was not selected, enter patient information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constellation™ settings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/constellation_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/constellation_settings/</guid>
      <description>To access the Constellation™ Overlay options, click Constellation™.
1 Opacity slider &amp;ndash; Lower the slider to make the overlay text more transparent or raise the slider to make the overlay text less transparent.  2 Show on-screen toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Constellation™ data to show on the display.  3 Imaging Mode Linking toggle switch &amp;ndash; Automatically switches system imaging modes when a Constellation™ surgical step is changed. The default imaging modes are used for linking and are created if they do not already exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centurion™ Settings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/centurion_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:44:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/centurion_settings/</guid>
      <description>To access the Centurion™ Overlay options, click Centurion™.
1 Opacity slider &amp;ndash; Lower the slider to make the overlay text more transparent or raise the slider to make the overlay text less transparent.  2 Enlarge Overlay toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enlarges the overlay features.  3 Show Only in Recording toggle switch &amp;ndash; Hides Centurion™ overlay information during operation, but displays it in recordings. NOTE: If the Centurion™ overlay is displayed on-screen, enable the record DataFusion toggle in Recording settings to capture the overlays in recorded video files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Layout</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/screen_layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:44:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/screen_layout/</guid>
      <description>To access the Screen Layout options, click Screen Layout. To set basic layout features, click Basic. To set advanced layout features, click Advanced.
1 Patient Info drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Sets the frequency in which patient information displays during operation.  2 PiP Location &amp;ndash; Sets the screen corner to display input from the secondary source during PiP layout. This option applies only when Secondary Viewport is set to PiP.  3 Secondary Viewport buttons &amp;ndash; Sets the layout for a secondary viewport the Screen Layout button switches to when clicked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording Settings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/recording_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/recording_settings/</guid>
      <description>To access Recording options, click Recording.
NOTICERecording settings cannot be changed while recording video.Basic and Advanced To set basic settings, click Basic. To set advanced settings, click Advanced.
1 Movies Format buttons &amp;ndash; Saves video files as .avi or .mov files.  2 Show Logo toggle switch &amp;ndash; Displays the system logo in the bottom-left corner during operation if Record DataFusion is disabled.  3 Auto-Record toggle switch &amp;ndash; Automatically starts recording when a case starts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Channel Management</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/color_channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/color_channels/</guid>
      <description>To access Color Channel options, click Color Channel. The system previews adjusted color channels in the Color Channel dialog box.
Editing Color Channels  Click an existing color channel. Click Edit. In the Name field, enter a new name if needed. Adjust the sliders to place emphasis on certain colors. Enable Advanced Settings to adjust brightness, contrast, gamma correction, hue, and saturation.  Adding Color Channels  Click Add. In the Name field, enter a descriptive name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Profile Settings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/light_profile_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/light_profile_settings/</guid>
      <description>Light profile settings correct color for different illumination sources. To access Light Profile options, click Light Profile. Alcon recommends matching the illumination source with the corresponding light profile.
1 Light Source selection &amp;ndash; Sets the applicable light source type.  2 White Balance button &amp;ndash; Sets white balance for the selected light source. Follow the on-screen instructions to complete the process. White balance optimizes image quality. Perform this process when the microscope or endo-illumination settings change, the lamps change, or the image quality or color balances are not optimized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imaging Mode Management</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/imaging_mode_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/imaging_mode_management/</guid>
      <description>Imaging modes are a core visualization baseline for routine cases. To access Imaging Mode options, click Imaging Mode. If operating with different illumination sources or optical systems that require inverted camera orientation, Alcon recommends creating a custom imaging mode to accommodate individual surgical workflows.
The default imaging modes include the following:
   Imaging Mode Camera Orientation Light Profile     Anterior Standard Halogen   Posterior Inverted Constellation™   Macular Standard Constellation™    To copy, edit, or delete imaging modes, click Unlock and then Confirm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/language/</guid>
      <description>The Language system settings control the language the system displays. Contact Technical Services for additional languages.
 To change the language, perform the following:
 In the Language drop-down menu, select a language. Click Confirm.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Procedure</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/shutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/shutdown/</guid>
      <description> On the Home screen, click Power. Click Shut Down. Wait for the EPU indicators next to the USB connectors (see Cart) to turn off (~30 s). Turn off the power switch at the base of the cart.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Clean the system by periodically wiping down with a dry, lint-free cloth. Use warm water and mild detergent on non-electrical system components (for example, the cart, exterior cart panels, and 3D glasses). Wipe down the camera and camera cable with isopropyl alcohol. Wipe the display with a soft, dry cloth. Use less than 0.10 lb. of force on the display. Water-based cleaners may damage the coating on the screen.  WARNINGOnly factory-authorized personnel should service the system or system components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage and Transportation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/storage/</guid>
      <description>To store or transport the system within the facility, perform the following:
 Route the camera cable.
a. Disconnect the camera cable from the camera.
b. Wrap camera cable around the camera cable coil. Route the power cable.
a. Disconnect the power cable from the outlet.
b. Wrap power cable around the power cable coil. If the system includes a connected DataFusion device, disconnect the cable on the other device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alcon Service</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:24:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/service/</guid>
      <description>For product service, please contact Alcon’s Technical Services Department at the number provided below. Operators experiencing problems with the system should refer to the Operating Instructions and Troubleshooting sections of this manual. A problem which persists should be referred to the Alcon Technical Services Department or your local authorized service representative.
For optimum performance, it is the user’s responsibility to schedule preventive maintenance service on the system and its accessories a minimum of one time per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microscope Alignment</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/microscope_alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/microscope_alignment/</guid>
      <description>Use the microscope controls to focus the image on-screen. If the image still appears out of focus or blurry, check the camera alignment using the crosshair target on the back of the white balance card.
 Put on 3D glasses and ensure a live image is observed on the system. Place the crosshair target face-up on a flat surface. Center the microscope field of view on the crosshair. Align the horizontal and vertical bars with the field of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Retention</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/image_retention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/image_retention/</guid>
      <description>Image retention is similar to a screen burn or ghosting shown on the display. To refresh the display pixels, press the Power button either on the display for about 3 seconds or the remote control. The display power indicator flashes while the process is in progress.
NOTICESome displays take about 10 minutes to begin the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K830 Keyboard Recharging</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/keyboard_recharge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/basic/keyboard_recharge/</guid>
      <description>To charge the K830 keyboard, use the micro USB cable to connect the keyboard to a USB connector on the cart. The battery indicator blinks green while charging. Charge it until the indicator light stops blinking. The keyboard can be used while charging. If the battery power is low, the indicator blinks red and the keyboard back light turns off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/maintenance/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>If the system exhibits the following symptoms, attempt the corresponding troubleshooting procedures before contacting Technical Services.
The image is blurry or out of focus.  Use the microscope controls to focus the image on-screen. Check to see that the camera is flush on the microscope. Wearing the 3D glasses, close one eye at a time to check the right and left eye focus for the camera. Change the camera orientation and note if the issue remains in the same location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External USB Drives</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/external_drives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/external_drives/</guid>
      <description>To transfer recorded video or snapshots to an external hard drive, connect the drive to a USB 3.0 connector (recommended) on the cart side panel or a USB 2.0 connector on the cart front panel. The drive must be in exFAT format. Alcon recommends using only 1 drive at a time.
NOTICEDo not connect or use an external hard drive during surgery. If the hard drive is protected or has a password, unlock the drive before use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constellation™ Control</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/constellation_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/constellation_control/</guid>
      <description>A connected Constellation™ can provide basic system commands to the system. Refer to the Constellation™ documentation for details on the Constellation™ interface.
NOTICEChanges to the light profile and color channel affect the selected imaging mode.During Constellation™ footswitch navigation, it is not possible to navigate backwards after selecting a submenu. Instead, close and open the menu again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/keyboard_shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:03:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/keyboard_shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>   Key Description     S Take a snapshot   R Start or stop a recording   Ctrl+FN+F1 Swap viewport layout   Ctrl+FN+F2 Swap video source   Ctrl+FN+F3 Switch camera orientation   Ctrl+FN+F4 Cycle imaging modes   Ctrl+FN+F5 Cycle light profiles   Ctrl+FN+F6 Cycle color channels   Ctrl+Insert Increase gain (digitally brighten)   Ctrl+Delete Decrease gain (digitally darken)   W+W White balance   Ctrl+Enter Start case (from the Home screen)   Ctrl+FN+End (K830) or Ctrl+FN+Right Arrow (K600) Shutdown (from the Home screen) or save media and then shutdown (from the Case screen)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disposal</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/disposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/additional_information/disposal/</guid>
      <description>This product complies with the WEEE Directive (2002/96/EC) marking requirement. Do not discard this electronic product in domestic household waste. This is an explanation of how to dispose of this product based on Waste Electrical and Electronic Equipment (WEEE), Directive 2002/96/EC. This directive is only valid in the EU. With reference to the equipment types in the WEEE directive Annex 1, this product is classified as a “Medical Device” product. Do not dispose in domestic household waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMC Compliance</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/emc_compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/emc_compliance/</guid>
      <description>The NGENUITY™ system is designed to work in the Professional Healthcare facility environment.
The NGENUITY™ system requires special precautions regarding EMC and needs to be installed and put into service according to the EMC information provided in the below tables.
The NGENUITY™ system is a medical device designated for Indoor Use Only.
WARNING Use of this system adjacent to or stacked with other equipment should be avoided because it could result in improper operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguards for Use with Other Medical Equipment</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/safeguards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/safeguards/</guid>
      <description>CAUTION All equipment connected to this unit shall be certified according to IEC 60601-1 or other IEC/ISO standards applicable to the equipment. Furthermore, all complete configurations shall comply with IEC 60601-1. If the user connects additional equipment to the signal input or signal output, this alters the medical device system, and it is then the user’s responsibility that the system complies with the requirements of the standard IEC 60601-1. If in doubt, contact Alcon Technical Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidance and Manufacturer Declaration - Electromagnetic Emissions</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/electromagnetic_emissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/electromagnetic_emissions/</guid>
      <description>The NGENUITY™ system is intended for use in the electromagnetic environments specified below. The customer or the user of the*NGENUITY™ system should assure it is used in such an environment.
   Emissions Test Compliance Electromagnetic Environment - Guidance     RF Emissions (CISPR 11) Group 1 The system uses RF energy only for its internal functions. Therefore, its RF emissions are low and are not likely to cause any interference in nearby electronic equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidance and Manufacturer Declaration - Electromagnetic Immunity</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/electromagnetic_immunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/emc_compliance/electromagnetic_immunity/</guid>
      <description>The NGENUITY™ system is intended for use in the electromagnetic environments specified below. The customer or the user of the NGENUITY™ system should assure it is used in such an environment.
   Immunity Test IEC 60601 Test and Compliance Level Electromagnetic Environment - Guidance      Electrostatic Discharge (IEC 61000-4-2) +/-8 kV contact, +/-15 kV air Floors should be wood, concrete, or ceramic tile. If floors are covered with synthetic material, the relative humidity should be at least 30%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cart (Communication Link with Centurion)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/comm_link/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/comm_link/</guid>
      <description> Frequency or frequency band of transmission: 2.405 GHz to 2.480 GHz Type and frequency characteristics of the modulation: OQPSK (Offset quadrature phase-shift keying) Effective Radiated Power (ERP): 11.3 dBm (13.40 mW)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA - Federal Communications Commission (FCC)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/fcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/fcc/</guid>
      <description>This device complies with part 15 of the FCC Rules. Operation is subject to the following two conditions: (1) This device may not cause harmful interference, and (2) this device must accept any interference received, including interference that may cause undesired operation.
CAUTIONChange or modifications made to this equipment (including the antenna) not expressly approved by the Company may void the FCC authorization to operate this equipment.FCC Radiation Exposure Statement WARNINGTo ensure that the radio transmitter complies with current FCC regulations limiting both maximum output RF power and human exposure to radio frequency radiation, a separate distance of at least 20 cm must be maintained between the unit’s antenna and the body of the user and any nearby persons at all times, and unit’s antenna must not be co-located or operating in conjunction with any other antenna or transmitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU - RED Directive 2014/53/EU</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/red_directive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/red_directive/</guid>
      <description>This device complies with the essential requirements of the Radio Equipment Directive 2014/53/ EU.
CAUTIONThe radio equipment is intended to be used in all EU and AFTA countries. Outdoor use may be restricted to certain frequencies and/or may require a license for operation. Contact local Authority for procedure to follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canada - Industry of Canada (IC)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/ic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/ic/</guid>
      <description>This device complies with Industry Canada license-exempt RSS standards. Operation is subject to the following two conditions: (1) This device may not cause harmful interference, and (2) this device must accept any interference, including interference that may cause undesired operation of the device.
Canada - Industrie du Canada (IC) Cet appareil est conforme aux normes d’Industrie Canada RSS exemptes de licence. Son fonctionnement est soumis aux deux conditions suivantes: (1) Cet appareil ne doit pas provoquer d’interférences nuisibles, et (2) cet appareil doit accepter toute interférence, y compris les interférences pouvant provoquer un fonctionnement indésirable de l’appareil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cart Wireless Certifications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_cart/</guid>
      <description>  United States FCC ID: RI7XE61
  Australia:
   Brazil:
   Canada IC ID: 5131A-XE61
  Japan:
 209-J00129     Korea:
 MSIP-CRI-TCS-X61-24, R-R-Alc-NGEN     Taiwan:
 CAAJ1LP2610T9     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K830 Wireless Keyboard Certifications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_k830/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_k830/</guid>
      <description>  United States FCC ID: JNZR0047
  Asia Pacific:
 N231, Z855     Brazil Anatel ID: MT-0788/2010
  Canada IC ID: 4418A-YR0047
  China CMIIT ID: 2010DJ0355
  EU:
 EU Certification     Japan:
 204-430004     Mexico IFT ID: CFT/CT/0084/12/TS
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K600 Wireless Keyboard Certifications</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_k600/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/wireless_certification/wireless_certificates_k600/</guid>
      <description>  United States FCC ID: JNZYR0068
  Asia Pacific:
   Brazil Anatel ID: 02904-18-03229
  Canada IC ID: 4418A-YR0068
  China CMIIT ID: 2018DJ2999
  Japan:
 020-180066     Korea: R-CRM-DZL-Y-R0068
  Taiwan: CCAI18LP0670T0
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Label Locations</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</guid>
      <description>Note the safety and system label locations. Refer to the system for specific information.
1 Moving parts warning label &amp;ndash; Includes a warning related to a protective guard.  2 Identifies compatible connectors. &amp;ndash; The location and connector type varies with the display model.  3 Oculars storage warning label &amp;ndash; Includes information about storing the microscope oculars.  4 Product label &amp;ndash; Includes information about the system.  5 Wireless label &amp;ndash; Indicates wireless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serious incident Reporting</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/serious_incident_reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/system_information/safety_information/serious_incident_reporting/</guid>
      <description>Any serious incident related to the use of this medical device should be reported to Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
  By phone: In USA – (800) 757-9780
In EU/International – Contact the local country office or your Alcon distributor.
  By website: http://www.alcon.com/contact-us/
  By email: qa.complaints@alcon.com
  These serious incidents should also be reported to the competent authority for medical devices of your Member State.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataFusion</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/datafusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/datafusion/</guid>
      <description>The DataFusion settings determine which device is connected to the system. To access DataFusion options, click DataFusion. The system can only enable one device at a time.
1 Constellation™ toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Constellation™ connection.  2 Centurion™ toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Centurion™ connection.  3 Edit button &amp;ndash; Opens a dialog box to connect to a specific device.  To connect to a Centurion™, perform the following:
  Click Edit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Input Source</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/input_source/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/input_source/</guid>
      <description>The input source controls which port is displayed in the secondary view. To set the secondary input source, click Input Source.
NOTICENo other sources are available for systems with a connected ORA SYSTEM&amp;trade;.In the View 2 panel, select one of the following:
 HDMI – Displays the input source from a connected ORA SYSTEM™. Composite – Displays the input source connected to the front panel composite connector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/system_settings/monitor/</guid>
      <description>The monitor system settings have adjustable settings for displays connected to the system. To access Monitor options, click Monitor.
Basic Monitor Settings WARNINGOnly the provided monitor should be used as the Primary Monitor.1 Monitor drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Selects a display.  2 Primary Monitor toggle switch &amp;ndash; Sets the selected display to the primary display.  3 View drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Sets the content on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagnostics</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/diagnostics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/diagnostics/</guid>
      <description>The Diagnostics system settings help troubleshooting issues with the system. The system generates and exports system diagnostics logs to an external USB drive.
To export logs, perform the following:
 Connect a USB drive. Click Diagnostics. Click Export Technician Log.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:48:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc/operation/settings/about/</guid>
      <description>The About system settings displays general system information, including software version and a copy of the user guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
